他在这个镇上神出鬼没 行踪不定
He moves through this town unseen, like a ghost,
每一年他肆意行凶
and he kills at will every year.
布利斯菲尔德屠夫在1977年开始了他的恐怖统治
The Blissfield Butcher started his reign of terror in 1977,
直至今日
and it continues to this day.
一个老年连环杀手吗
A geriatric serial killer?
当真
Really?
别低估一个白人直男的暴力倾向 艾萨克
Don't underestimate a straight white man's propensity for violence, Isaac.
我他妈才不关心他们有多老
I don't care how fucking old they are.
还有你的故事就是扯淡 埃文
And your story... it's bullshit, Evan.
那屠夫在九十年代的时候 杀害了几个年轻人
The Butcher killed some kids, like, in the '90s,
然后二十年前 他消失了
and then 20 years ago, he disappeared.
剩下的就只是民间传说了
The rest is just local folklore.
是啊 但是屠夫那会儿 不是也在毕业舞会上
Yeah, but didn't the Butcher, like, also kill
杀了一群孩子么
a bunch of kids at prom way back when?
不是毕业舞会返校节
Not prom. Homecoming.
所有布利斯菲尔德屠夫的故事都围绕着返校节
All the Blissfield Butcher stories are centered around homecoming.
每一年的返校节期间
And a new legend pops up every year
都会有一个新的传说出现
during homecoming week to warn Blissfield's teenagers
警告布利斯菲尔德的青少年 注意未成年人放荡的危险
of the dangers of "underage debauchery."
今年的故事又会是什么
What will this year's story be?
天啊 艾萨克
Oh, my God, Isaac!
我现在闻着像廉价的啤酒
I smell like cheap beer now.
嘿 吧台那有些苏打水 通常都能解决这问题
Hey, there's some soda water in the bar. That usually helps.
这些都是什么鬼东西
What is all this shit?
吉妮的爸爸是个艺术收藏家
Ginny's dad's an art collector.
那挺酷的
That's pretty cool.
嗯
Hmm.
哇哦
Wow.
拉多拉是什么玩意儿
The fuck's La Dola?
嘿 这东西压根打不开
Hey, there's no way to open this thing.
你到底帮不帮我
Are you gonna help me or not?
呃你这态度可不行
Uh, not with that attitude.
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm!
好家伙这才是我要找的
Now, that's what I'm talking about.
蒙
Mon...
蒙特蒙特拉
Montra... Montrach...
蒙特拉奇
Montrachet?
噢 我操
Oh, shit.
干得好 桑德拉 你害我把它砸地上了
Yeah, nice one, Sandra. You made me drop it.
真是的
God.
天啊 他们会杀了我的
God, they're gonna kill me.
这酒看起来好贵
This looks so expensive.
该死
Damn it.
你总该下来帮我一块打扫吧
You know, you could at least come down and help me clean this up.
你这态度可不行呢
"Not with that attitude."
随你的便 艾萨克
Whatever, Isaac.
请等一下
One moment, please.
砸门也没用我说了等一下
Aggro-knocking won't make me move any faster.
等等我还没好呢
Wait. What about me?
你也太久了
You're taking too long.
我那是个阴道 可不是个通宵服务的得来速
It's a vagina, not an all-night drive-through.
我们能再来个三分钟么 我只要求这么多
Can we go three more minutes? That's all I need.
你也太不体谅别人了
You know, that's really inconsiderate.
是嘛 因为男生都可会体谅人了呢
Yeah, 'cause guys are always so considerate.
那帮我打个飞机行不行
Maybe a handy?
救命
Help!
爸爸
Daddy.
你看到车道尽头的那辆车了吗
Did you see the car at the end of the driveway?
没有我看到了
- No. - I did.
她最好别带男孩子回家
She better not have boys over.
要是她带来了 我他妈就
Oh, if she does, I'm gonna fucking...
啊我的天啊
Oh, my God!
米莉 吃早饭了
Millie, breakfast!
一早安早
- Good morning. - Morning.
好香啊
It smells so good.
香蕉煎饼 凯斯勒的传家秘方
Banana pancakes, Kessler family recipe.
嗯
Mmm.
-﻿我打包带路上吃咯 -嘿  不行 不行
- I'll take mine to go. - Hey. No, no, no.
过来坐下
Come sit down.
让我们像一家人一样坐下吃饭
Let's eat like a family for a change.
一家人是哦
Family. Right.
瞧这样多好呀
See? Isn't this nice?
感觉我们几乎再也没这样吃过饭了
It feels like we hardly ever do this anymore
自从你们爸爸
since your-your dad...
那么米莉
So, Millie,
明天的返校节你有伴吗
do you have a date for homecoming tomorrow?
我 呃 我不 我不去了
I, um... I'm not... I'm not going.
她跟我约好了
She has a date with me.
我们明天去肛妮斯剧院看魔法坏女巫
We're going to see Wicked at the Anus Theater.
是安妮丝剧院
"Ann-is."
哇哦
Wow.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
就感觉为了和妈妈去个破烂的地区剧院
It just seems a little weird to miss out on a seminal high school experience
而错过一次开创性的高中经历有一点奇怪吧
to go see shit regional theater with your mom.
噢  不好意思 难道你不该劝阻她
Oh, I'm sorry. Aren't you supposed to discourage her
不要去参与这类活动么
from things like that?
返校节就是一群未成年人饮酒
You know it's just underage drinking
然后天晓得会导致什么悲剧
and God knows what else that can end in tragedy.
哦 她明晚依旧会以悲剧告终
Oh, her night is still ending in tragedy.
夏琳
Charlene.
你想跟我去的 你是为之兴奋的对吗 米莉
Yeah, I mean, you want to go. You're excited, right, Millie?
是的当然了
Yeah. Of course.
我得走了长官说有急事
I got to go. The sheriff says it's urgent.
嗯
Mmm.
煎饼 真的很好吃 妈
Pancakes are really good, Mom.
噢  谢谢亲爱的
Oh. Thanks, honey.
跟上了 女士们
Keep up, ladies.
早上好 米莉
Morning, Millie.
嗨 丹尼尔斯先生
Hi , Mr. Daniels.
打个招呼
Say hello.
你好呀你好可爱
Hello. You're so cute.
人家好喜欢你的黑腊肠哦 丹尼尔斯先生
I love your black wiener, Mr. Daniels.
乔舒亚
Joshua.
那腊肠狗是黑色的 奈拉
The dog is black, Nyla.
我们走远点吧
Let's go far.
天啦
Oh, my God.
-我 我去不了 -米莉 你答应过的
- I-I couldn't. - Millie, you promised.
我知道 但是她让我感觉好内疚
I know, but she made me feel so bad.
你妈的超能力就是让你内疚
Your mom's superpower is guilt.
这下你要为了去看个挂在电线上的绿脸女巫
Now you're gonna miss the homecoming dance
而错过返校节舞会了
to go watch some hag in green face hanging from a wire?
拜托硬气一点
Come on. Tit up.
就是个愚蠢的舞会 你们又为啥那么想去呢
It's just a stupid dance. Why do you want to go, anyway?
我要给班级纪念册拍照
I have to shoot it for yearbook.
我是冲着那些醉醺醺的直男去的 他们会瞬间觉得自己没那么直啦
I'm in it for the drunk straight boys who will suddenly realize they're fluid.
一听着有点变态那就好
- That sounds kind of rapey. - Good.
你知道这镇上都是些什么货色么
Have you seen what's on the menu in this town?
这不是那个邮差么 -我的妈呀
- Is that the mailman? - Oh, my God.
欢迎来到悲惨世界
Welcome to Tragicstan.
-﻿还有噢  -噢  天啊
- And hello. - Oh , my...
伯克到时候会在场
Booker is gonna be at the dance.
这是你搞定他的机会
This is your chance to land that plane.
我不想搞定他或者任何人
I'm not landing that plane or any plane.
他几乎都不知道我的存在
He hardly knows I exist.
你认真的吗 你他妈可是个辣妹
Are you serious? You're a fucking piece, girl.
-哦 我是个辣妹 -嗯哼
- Oh, I'm a piece? - Uh-huh.
好吧 不管用词是否恰当 乔舒亚是对的
Okay, barf choice of words or not, Joshua's right.
你可以的 米莉你得承认这点
You got it, Mill. You just need to own it.
是吧连文字警察小姐都认同
See? Even Miss Word Police agrees.
你要去参加噢 说定了
You're going. That's final.
嘿 米莉 等一下
Hey, Mill, hold on a sec.
已经一年了
It's been a year.
你不能一直为别人活着
You can't keep living your life for someone else.
你得开始为自己考虑了
You've got to start doing things for you.
是啊 只是
Yeah, it's just...
没那么简单
It's not that easy.
我爸是她的全世界
My dad was her whole world.
我明白我真的懂
I get it. I really do.
你不想伤你妈的心
You don't want to hurt your mom's feelings.
这也是为什么我爱你的原因
It's why I love you.
我只是我不想你哪天早上醒来
I just... I don't want you to wake up one morning
意识到你的整个人生已经与你擦肩而过因为你忙于取悦别人
and realize your whole life passed you by 'cause you were busy being everything
而没有为自己活过
to everyone but you.
干餐时候见 好吗
I'll see you at lunch, okay?
爱你噢 爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
米莉 嗨
Millie, hi.
嗨  莱勒
Hi, Ryler.
我喜欢你的裙子
I love your dress.
谢谢你哪里买的
- Thanks. - Where'd you get it?
我不知道
I... don't know.
我 呃 已经买来很久了
I, um... I've had it a long time.
我好像在伯南扎折扣店看到过
I think I saw it at Discount Bonanza.
我那会儿去里面借个厕所
I had to pee.
你妈是不是用了员工折扣
Did your mom use her employee discount?
不管怎样 你看起来很可爱噢  真心的
Anyway, you look adorbs, seriously.
天啊
God.
噢  我的
Oh, my...
我做了个常见的金字塔型
And I did a common A-frame,
但是窗框上的细节是很讲究的
but with delicate detail to the window framing.
任何狗狗都会为了得到这个房子而疯狂
Any dog would kill to call this their home.
要是你安装个喇叭
If you installed some speakers,
放上个小毯子 它将成为终极的狗狗之家
threw down a rug, it'd be the ultimate pooch pad.
不好意思 贝纳迪先生
Sorry, Mr. Bernardi.
-﻿又迟到了 凯斯勒小姐 -不会再有下次了
- Late again, Miss Kessler. - It won't happen again.
我深表怀疑坐下吧
I doubt that. Just sit down.
非常好
It's very nice.
这个木制品非常出色
This woodwork is exceptional.
谢谢 贝先生 -嘿
- Thanks, Mr. B. - Hey.
专业人士建议闹钟永远设置提前五分钟
Pro tip: always set your watch five minutes ahead.
对我来说很管用 几乎每一次都是
It saves my ass, like, every time.
谢啦
Thanks.
狗狗城堡
Château Fido.
来点掌声
Come on.
干的不错 菲尔
Great work, Phil.
再一次提高了本班的水准
Once again, setting the class standard.
下一位是
Next up is...
噢 米莉·凯斯勒
Oh, Millie Kessler.
是时候为大家展示你的狗房子了
Time to present your doghouse.
呃我的展示得等到下周
Uh, my presentation isn't scheduled till next week.
这里不是辩论课
This isn't debate class.
可是你说过是十六号
But you said the 16th.
我还没准备好
Um, it's not ready yet.
凯斯勒小姐又在耽误全班时间了
Once again, Miss Kessler is holding up the class.
凯斯勒小姐又一次没做好准备
And once again, Miss Kessler is unprepared.
混蛋
Dick.
有什么要补充的吗 伯克
Something to add, Booker?
没有
Nope.
我能十六号再交吗
Can I just... do it the 16th?
Can I just do it the 16th?
大声点
Speak up.
噢 鳄鱼眼泪可不能为你的计划不周 开脱凯斯勒小姐
Oh, crocodile tear doesn't excuse your poor planning, Miss Kessler.
我的妈
My God.
这简直太疯狂了
This is completely bonkers.
我都震惊了
I'm in shock.
我两天前还在体育课上见过桑德拉
I just saw Sandra two days ago in PE.
而现在她已经
And now she's...
天啊 简直是个屠宰场
Oh, my God. It's a slaughterhouse.
你在笑吗
Are you smiling?
大家都吓坏了
Everybody is freaking out.
瞧瞧这个
Check it out.
吉妮是我最好的朋友之一
Ginny was one of my best friends.
为什么
Why?
婊子 省省吧
Bitch, please.
吉妮恨死莱勒了
Ginny hated Ryler
她在外放谣言说吉妮把一根胡萝卜
after she started that rumor about Ginny getting a carrot
塞进自己逼里别说那个字
- stuck in her pussy. - Don't say that word.
随便啦阴道
Whatever. Vagina.
谁会做出这种事
Who would do something like this?
布利斯菲尔德屠夫
The Blissfield Butcher.
他只是个都市传说他不是真的
He's just an urban legend. He's not real.
四个惨死的青少年
Mmm, four very dead teens.
对我来说挺真实的
It seems pretty real to me.
他们得取消返校节舞会了
They're gonna have to cancel homecoming.
得了吧
Please.
返校节舞会就相当于这里的圣诞节
Homecoming is like Christmas around here.
他们不会取消的
They're not canceling it.
早就告诉你了
Told ya.
万岁 万岁 布利斯菲尔德高中
Hail, hail, Blissfield High!
喀嚓喀嚓喀嚓 我们的战争呐喊
Chomp, chomp, chomp, our battle cry!
哟 哥们瞧好了
Yo, guys, check this, check this.
当我们的海狸来战斗感受 我们的自豪与力量
When our Beavers come to fight, feel our glory and our might!
唯一一个没人想碰的海狸( beaver在英语里有女性生殖器的意思)
Only beaver nobody would touch!
你要是把她脸遮起来 还是能日得下去的
I mean, if you brown-bag her face, she's sort of doable.
我闻起来像橘子汽水
I smell like orange soda.
没那么糟啦
It's not that bad.
你该退出这根本不值得
You should quit. It is not worth it.
参与课外活动对申请大学有帮助
Extracurriculars look good on applications.
好像你妈会让你离开去上大学似的
As if your mom would ever let you go away to college.
嘿
Hey.
她又迟到了
She's late. Again.
你确定不用别人送吗 -嗯
- You sure you don't want a ride? - Yeah.
她会来的 可能停车加油去了
Yeah, she'll be here. She probably just stopped for gas.
要我们陪你一起等吗 -不用
- You want us to wait with you? - Mmm-mmm.
外面有个变态在乱窜噢
There is a psycho roaming free.
不用啦
No.
我没事的边上有这么多人呢
I'm good. There's plenty of people around.
她很快就来了
And she'll be here any minute.
我没事的你们走吧
I'm good. Just go.
好吧
Okay.
再见 米莉
Bye, Mill.
-再见 爱你噢  -再见 爱你 小卷毛
- Bye. Love you. - Bye-bye. Love you, poodle.
非常感谢你们
Thank you very much.
-爱你 -爱你
- Love you. - Love you.
再见再见
- Bye. - Bye!
现在只要46 立马送到你手上
And it's yours, right now, for only 46...
我靠
Goddamn it.
妈的
Shit.
嗨
Hi.
她又在沙发上睡过去了
She's passed out on the couch again.
你能来接
Can you come get...
你跟我开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me right now.
她将
She'll be
她将绕过大山而来
Comin' round the mountain when she comes
She'll be comin' round The mountain when she comes
她将绕过大山而来
She'll be comin' round the mountain
他将
He'll be comin'...
千万不要是屠夫
Please don't be the Butcher.
千万不要是屠夫千万不要是屠夫
Please don't be the Butcher. Please don't be the Butcher.
我姐姐马上就到了
My sister's gonna be here any second!
她是个警察
She's a cop!
配枪的
With a gun!
该死
Shit.
救命救救我
Help! Help me!
救命
Help!
不要啊
No!
不
不不要啊
No! No!
不
No!
不不不不
No! No! No! No!
不要啊
No!
放开她
Get away from her!
米莉米莉
Millie! Millie!
天啊
Oh, my God!
6542请求支援
6542 to dispatch.
我需要一辆救护车尽快到达我的位置
I need an ambulance at my location ASAP!
嘿
Hey.
你没事的你没事的
You're okay. You're okay.
-﻿他也受伤了 -你受惊了 没事了
- It hurt him, too. - You're in shock. It's okay.
-﻿救援已经来了好吗 -他也受伤了
- Help's coming, okay? - It hurt him, too.
没事了没事了救援来了
It's okay. It's okay. Help's coming.
救援在路上了
Help's on the way.
你会没事的你会没事的
You're gonna be okay. You're gonna be okay.
你要我们陪你一起等吗
You want us to wait with you?
外面有个变态在乱窜噢
There is a psycho roaming free.
这里有那么多人呢
There's plenty of people around.
她马上就到了
She'll be here any minute.
米莉米莉
Millie! Millie!
天啊 发生了什么
Oh, my God! What happened?
你怎么了
What happened to you?
噢  我的天啊
Oh, my God!
不 这不是我的错
No, it wasn't my fault!
我知道但是我只是回到家
I know. But I was just coming home.
想睡到四点半左右
I was gonna sleep until 4:30.
我太累了又喝了一杯酒
I was so tired. I had one glass of wine.
你喝了不止一杯酒
You did not have one glass of wine!
你喝了一整瓶酒
No, you had an entire bottle of wine to drink.
就只有一杯酒 -行吧
- It was one glass of wine! - Yeah, right.
一觉睡到早上
Sleep till morning.
休息睡觉
Rest. Sleep.
拉多拉
La Dola.
嘿
Hey.
太好了你起来了
Good. You're up.
感觉怎样
How are you feeling?
好吧 那么
Okay, then.
你的肩膀怎么样了
How's your shoulder?
要不这样
You know what?
下班后 我们去做美甲吧
Let's go get manicures after work, huh?
好吧 我给你点时间调整下
Okay, then. Well, I'm gonna give you a minute.
我做了法式吐司配了 你最喜欢的
And, uh, I made French toast, with your favorite:
焦糖香蕉
caramelized bananas.
好吧
Okay.
米莉快点
Mill, come on.
早餐要凉啦
Food's getting cold.
我在哪里
Where am I?
有人吗
Hello?
天呐 我声音怎么变这样了
Oh, my God. Why do I sound like that?
什么鬼东西 我的妈
What the fuck? Oh, Jesus.
好了你只是出现幻觉了
Okay. You are just hallucinating.
-嘿 你有吉利豆吗 -我不明白
- Hey! You got any jelly beans? - I'm sorry.
我有吉利豆吗 -你懂的冰块
- Do I have jelly beans? - You know, ice cubes.
爆米花 你有可卡因吗 老哥
Uh, crunch and munch. You got some drugs, man?
噢 天啊 我什么可卡因都没有
Oh, my God. No, I don't have any drugs.
我不吸毒
I'm not a drug person.
呃 我能问你个问题吗
Uh, may I ask you a question?
-啥 -就是 你知道
- What? - Yeah. Just, you know,
我想知道 我看起来怎么样
I'm just curious. What do I look like?
你现在看着我对吧
Like, when you're seeing me right now?
我看起来像个 呃 我看起来像个女孩子吗
Do I look like a, um, you know, do I look like a girl?
女孩子 -嗯
- Girl? - Yeah.
比如一米六五非常娇小的金发的那种
You know, like, five-foot-five. Very petite blond.
你他妈骗人呢
You're fucking lying, man.
你有毒品的 你现在不就嗑嗨 了
You, you, you got drugs. You're high right now.
噢 不不 我没有
Oh, no, no. I don't have the drugs.
拜托 老哥给我一点吧
Come on, man. Give me some of those.
劲儿也太猛了 -别这样别这样
- That's good stuff. - Please don't. Please don't.
我想体验下当少女的感受
I want to feel like a teenage girl. I want to feel like a girl.
我想体验下当少女的感受我说帮帮我
I said... Help me!
拜托回来啊回来
Come on! Come back! Come back!
我愿意舔你的鸡巴
I'll suck your dick!
连鸡带蛋
All of it!
我此时正位于布利斯菲尔德谷高中
I'm here just outside Blissfield Valley High School,
一位女学生在此被暴力袭击
where a teenage girl was viciously attacked.
该幸存者的名字 没有公布
The survivor, whose name is being withheld...
噢  嘿  甜心
Oh, hey, sweetie.
刚没看到你
I didn't see you there.
你像个小小忍者一样
You're like a little ninja.
来吧
Come on.
来 我给你做了早饭
Come on, I made you breakfast.
坐吧 傻孩子
Sit, silly.
来
Come on.
吃吧
Here you go.
我真的希望你能吃点好吗
I really want you to try to eat, okay?
给你买了新鲜的菠萝
Got you some fresh pineapple.
我知道你很喜欢菠萝
I know how much you love it.
这个水份也很多
It's a good juicy one, too.
噢
Oh.
妈妈把糖浆给忘了
Mama forgot the syrup.
给你淋上
There you go.
尽量吃点好吗
Try to eat something, okay?
嗯
Mmm.
脆脆的就是你喜欢的口感
Crispy, like you like it.
嗯
Mmm.
唔
噢  天啦
Oh. Oh, my word.
好吧 好吧 我猜你是饿了
Yeah, okay. All right. I guess you are hungry.
谁啊
Who on earth is...
嘿  凯斯勒夫人
Hey, Mrs. K.
嗨 弗兰克
Hi, Frank.
我本来打算把这个塞进你们邮箱的 但是想了下最好还是来看望下你们
I was gonna stick this in your box, but I figured I better check on y'all.
噢 好吧 谢谢你
Oh, okay. Well, thank you.
米莉还好吗
How... how's Millie?
我都听说了太糟糕了
I heard. It's just awful.
嗯
Well...
她受到了点惊吓 但是她会没事的
I think she's a little bit in shock, but she's gonna be okay.
妈 家里一股北岸餐厅的味道
Mom, this house smells like a fucking Denny's.
嘿
Hey.
我以为你还在睡呢
I thought you were still sleeping.
早上好噢
Good morning?
行吧
Okay.
交给我吧 甜心
I got it, sweetie.
再见 祝你一天愉快噢 亲爱的
- Bye. - Have a good day, honey.
注意安全 -谢了 妈
- Be safe. - Thanks, Mom.
好了
Okay.
宝贝 我觉得你应该再去休息一下
Honey, I think you should go and get some more rest.
你不会在想着要去学校吧
You're not thinking of going to school, are you?
学校
School?
我明白 你朋友一定都很担心你
I mean, I know your friends must be worried about you, but...
朋友
Friends.
犯罪嫌疑人
The suspect, now identified as
昆汀·谢默从阿文代尔疗养院出逃
Quentin Shermer, escaped the Avondale Sanatorium,
该疗养院是最高安全级别的关押精神病罪犯的监狱
a maximum-security facility for the criminally insane.
谢默也被当地人称为布利斯菲尔德屠夫
Shermer, also known by locals as the Blissfield Butcher,
1992年他谋杀了自己的母亲
murdered his mother and infamously left
并无耻地把母亲的头砍下丢在一家冰雪皇后店外
her severed head outside a Dairy Queen in 1992.
丹尼尔斯先生
Mr. Daniels?
丹尼尔斯先生 我是
Mr. Daniels, it's...
你是谁
Who are you?
没事的 -哦噢
- It's okay. Oh! - Oh!
天啊我很抱歉
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
是你
It's you.
-不是 -是他
- No. - It's him!
是他
It's him!
那该不会是
Is that...
她看着还挺漂亮
Does she look cute?
你这外套怎么回事米莉
What's with the outfit, Mill?
我不敢相信你妈今天居然让你来学校了
Uh, I can't believe your mom let you come to school today.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
哎哟笑一个
- Ow. - Smile for Insta.
米莉 你是布利斯菲尔德的受害者 我们爱你
Millie, you're Blissfield's victim. We love you.
-能别这样吗莱勒 -滚蛋莱勒
- Can you not, Ryler? - Piss off, Ryler.
这跟你没关系
This is not about you.
滚开
Fuck off.
看警方的那副素描画像 那人看着就像个杀手
And that police sketch... of course that guy's a killer.
那恶心的肿胀的汗津津的脸 还有褐色的牙齿
That gross, bloated, sweaty face and brown teeth.
我从没见过像他那么丑的人
I mean, I don't think I've ever seen anyone as hideous as that.
带我走 -去哪
- Take me. - Uh, where?
私密的
Someplace...
地方
private.
我的天
Oh, my God.
昨晚还发生了别的事对吗
Something else happened last night, didn't it?
你完全可以告诉我 我是最值得信任的人了
You can totally tell me. I'm, like, the most trustworthy person.
闻起来像热狗汤汁
Smells like hot dog water.
妈的
Fudge!
我是个巨人我是个巨人
I'm a giant. I'm a giant.
好了都告诉我吧
Okay. Tell me everything.
他有没有
Did he...
你懂的
You know.
我看过素描图我懂那些标记
I've seen "SVU." I know the signs.
呃喂
Uh, hello.
噢
Oh.
等等你是不是
Wait, are you...
我意思是如果你是也没关系
I mean, it's fine if you are.
怎么讲真的米莉我的预修生物课要来不及了
What? Honestly, Millie, I'm missing AP bio.
我来这不是跟你欲棒相争的
I didn't come here to clam-jam with you.
我今天差不多喝了十瓶红茶菌了
I've had, like, ten kombuchas today,
我得去尿尿了 等我回来的时候
so I'm gonna go pee, and when I get back,
你有料就爆 否则我就走人了
you're either spilling the tea or I'm out.
怪胎
Freak.
有人吗
Hello?
是米莉吗
Millie?
噢 噢 天啊
Oh. Oh, my God.
米莉屠夫在这里
Millie, The Butcher's here.
他在这里 我们得离开 -你得躲起来
- He's here. We need to go. - You need to hide.
什么
Wha...
你确定这样安全吗 -不确定
- Are you sure this is safe? - No.
不
No!
你搞什么啊
What was that?
米莉米莉米莉
Millie! Millie! Millie!
米莉回来
Millie, come back!
米莉米莉
Millie! Millie!
米莉
Millie!
舒服多了
Much better.
莱勒
Ryler.
鉴于我们的学生接连不断遭到袭击
Due to the continued attacks on our students,
经学校董事会还有拉金警长一致同意
together with the school board and Sheriff Larkin,
我决定无限期的延迟
I have decided to indefinitely postpone
今晚的返校节舞会
tonight's homecoming dance.
什么 -全市范围的宵禁
- What? - City-wide curfew
已经生效从今晚八点开始
is in effect, starting at 8:00 p.m.
警方将继续搜捕这名布利斯菲尔德屠夫
As police continue the manhunt for the Blissfield Butcher...
凯斯勒小姐
Miss Kessler.
我在跟你说话凯斯勒小姐
I'm speaking to you, Miss Kessler.
注意安全海狸们
Stay safe, Beavers.
嘿 你还好吗
Hey, how are you holding up?
会撩啊
Hot.
该死的米莉
Goddamn it, Millie.
你一个劲搔首弄姿 我真受够了
I am so sick of your constant need for attention.
你要是少花点时间调情
If only you would spend a little less time flirting
多花点时间学习
and a little more time learning,
你可能还真的能有所成就
you might actually make something out of yourself.
还没人影么 -我觉得她不会来了
- Still nothing? - I don't think she's coming.
她表现得怪怪的
She's acting weird.
她昨晚差点被杀了奈拉
She was almost killed last night, Ny.
她要古怪一天 我们也随她吧
Maybe we let her be weird for a day.
我就是担心她
I'm just worried about her.
奈拉别害怕
Nyla, don't freak out.
大伙们
Guys.
Guys!
大伙们大伙们听着不是你们想的那样
Guys, guys, listen. It's not what you think.
拜托
Come on!
蛋啊我有蛋
Balls. I got balls.
他还在跟着我们伙计们
- He's still following us! - Guys!
你是黑人 我是基佬 我们死定了
You're Black! I'm gay! We are so dead!
来人啊救命
Somebody help us, please!
奈拉乔什
Nyla! Josh!
别跑了 我不会伤害你们的
Stop running. I'm not gonna hurt you.
是我米莉
It's me. It's Millie.
你是有多变态 -他怎么知道我们名字的
- What kind of sick fuck are you? - How does he know our names?
-﻿别跑了 求你们了 -你他妈离我们远点
- Stop running, please. - You stay the fuck away from us!
奈拉 你能听我说句话吗
Nyla, will you listen to me for a second?
我操
Fuck!
噢 天啊 我好强壮
Oh, God, I'm strong.
-拜托 -奈拉 真对不起 我们好好谈一谈
- Come on! - Nyla, I'm so sorry. Let's just talk.
大伙们 不 别 别
Guys. No, don't, don't!
当真吗
Really?
乔什 大伙们 打住 你能住手吗 乔什
Josh! Guys, stop! Will you stop, Josh?
怎么你疯了吗
What, are you nuts?
哎哟 你们能别朝我砸东西了么 -乔什 打他
- Ow! Will you stop throwing things at me? - Josh, get him!
你得住手了
You got to stop!
乔什
Josh!
大伙们 听我说 哎哟
Guys! Okay, listen to me. Ow!
住手 住手
Stop it! Stop it.
住手
Stop it.
好了 退后 退后
Okay. Back up. Back up.
大伙们听我说
Guys, listen to me.
我没想伤害你们 好吗
I am not trying to hurt you, okay?
我要是想的话 我会把我的武器扔掉吗
If I was, would I drop my weapon?
我是你们的朋友
I'm your friend.
哎哟哎哟哎哟
Ow! Ow! Ow!
别打我了
Stop hitting me.
打人是不行的 乔什
Hitting's not okay, Josh.
哎哟
Ow!
开枪
Take the shot!
我没枪 -赶紧的
- I don't have one! - Just do it! Just take the...
好了 大家都累了吧
Okay. Everyone's tired. We've done lots of hitting.
打也打够了
It's time to talk.
是时候谈谈了
Hail, hail, Blissfield High.
万岁 万岁 布利斯菲尔德高中
Chomp, chomp, chomp's our battle cry.
喀嚓喀嚓是我们的战争呐喊 当我们的海狸来战斗
When our Beavers come to fight,
感受我们的自豪与力量
feel our glory and our might.
行了吗
Yeah?
你最喜欢的电影是什么
What's your favorite movie?
我跟别人都说是暖暖内含光
I tell people it's Eternal Sunshine,
但实际上是完美音调2
but it's Pitch Perfect 2.
-﻿电视剧呢 -萨布丽娜的惊心冒险
- TV show? - Sabrina.
最喜欢的零食 -三重浆果软糖
- Favorite snack. - Triple Berry Gushers.
你的暗恋对象是谁
Who's your biggest crush?
伯克·霍克
The Booker Hooker.
握手言和吧 婊子们
Shake, bitches.
没错吧
Right?
噢 我的天啊 -是啊
- Oh, my God! - Yes.
天啦等一下
Oh, my God.
这是怎么发生的 -这怎么可能
- Wait a minute. How did this happen? - How is that even possible?
你们猜怎么着 我急切需要一个朋友
And guess what, I need a friend right now,
而你们都朝我一个劲地砸东西
and it's like, you guys are smashing the shit out of me.
他拿了个长相奇怪的匕首捅了我
He stabbed me with this, like, weird, old-looking dagger,
但是他捅我的时候 我们都受伤了
but when he stabbed me, we both got hurt.
什么意思
What do you mean?
站着尿尿还是有点酷的
Standing and peeing is kind of rad.
米莉 专注点 -抱歉 什么
- Millie, focus. - Sorry? What?
你们两个都受伤了 -噢 是啊
- You both got hurt? - Oh. Yeah.
他捅我的时候 他立马也有了个伤口
So, when he stabbed me, he instantly got a wound, too,
但是是在同一个位置左肩部位
but in the exact same spot, the left shoulder.
然后昨天很晚的时候 我一直听到
And then, late last night, I kept hearing
匕首的名字 很奇怪的
the dagger's name, like, this weird,
就像在我脑子里窃窃私语 拉多拉 拉多拉
like, whispering in my head: "La Dola, La Dola."
我觉得是多拉引起这一切的
I think the Dola caused this.
这差不多三加仑的尿了 这家伙的膀胱也太庞大了
This is, like, three gallons of pee. This guy's bladder is huge.
其他部位也很大吗 -乔舒亚
- Is everything huge? - Joshua.
啥 你明白这里是男厕所 对吧
Wha... You know this is the boys' room, right?
她手里有根鸡巴 而你喷了 香奈儿五号
She's got a dick in her hand, and you're wearing Chanel No. 5.
没什么好大惊小怪了
Think we're past labels.
这也太奇葩了
This is ridiculous.
你们来瞧瞧这玩意儿 就像个软趴趴的食蚁兽
You guys got to see this. This is like a floppy anteater.
是这个吗
This it?
是的就是它
Yes, that's it.
就是这把匕首
That's the dagger.
拉多拉一把古老的阿兹特克匕首
"La Dola, an ancient Aztecan dagger
用于献祭仪式
"used in ritual sacrifice"?
尿完要擦一下吗 上面写着字
- Do I wipe? - There's writing on it.
我觉得是西班牙语
I think it's Spanish.
我看不懂
I can't read it.
你不是在西班牙语三班吗
Aren't you in Spanish Three?
你想说明什么
And your point?
你应该能看得懂西班牙语
You should be able to read Spanish.
那门课就没人是认真对待的
Nobody pays attention in that class.
我们要不找凯恩斯老师来翻译下吧
Why don't we get Señora Cayenes to translate it?
是什么意思
What does it say?
呃
Uh...
德特莫先生你是有上我的课的
Señor Detmer, you are in my class.
我有阅读障碍
Well, I'm dyslexic.
我有医生开的证明
I have a doctor's note.
这里说如果献祭不成功
It says here, if the sacrifice is not successful,
两个人的灵魂就会互换
the souls of the two persons are swapped
而变换将在二十四小时后变成永久
and the change becomes permanente after 24 hours.
永久
Permanent?
对
Sí.
男生真恶心
Boys are so gross.
噢 天啊你是认真的吗
Oh, my God. Are you serious?
我不是个吃鸡者
I'm not a cock gobbler.
快点 傻逼 我要撇大条了
Hurry up, loser. I got to take a dump.
对对不起先生 我不是故意打扰你的
Uh, I'm sorry, sir. I didn't mean to interrupt.
我 我是在找别人
I... I was... I was looking for, for someone else. I...
怎么样
How's that feel?
你喜欢恐惧的滋味吗
You like being scared?
不 对 对不起 我 我以为
No. I'm s... I'm sorry. I di... I thought
以为是
it was gonna be...
求你了
Please.
你要是再欺负米莉·凯斯勒
If you ever mess with Millie Kessler
或任何别的孩子 我发誓
or any other kid again, I swear,
我会让你这张丑陋的恶心的愚蠢的脸
I'll make you wish your buggy, wormy, stupid face
后悔来到这世上 明白了吗
was never born. Do you got it?
噢 天啊 你尿了吗
Oh, my God. Did you just pee yourself?
是的 -呕
- Yes! - Ew!
恶心死了
That's disgusting.
你是说如果我在午夜之前不拿那匕首捅他
So you're saying if I don't stab him with the Dola
我就要永远困在这个身体里了
by midnight, I'm gonna be stuck in this body forever?
对的 -还有大概九小时了
- Yep. - That's in, like, nine hours.
还是可行的差不多吧 -匕首在哪里
- Uh, it's doable. Adjacent. - Where's the Dola?
在警察局的证物室里
It's at the police station in the evidence locker.
那我们赶紧过去吧
Then we better get going over there now.
伙计们他就在这里的某个地方
Guys, he's here somewhere.
他披着我的皮囊和我的脸
And he's wearing my body and he's wearing my face.
他就像个披着羊皮的狼
He's like a wolf in sheep's clothing.
要是我们不先抓住他
And if we don't capture him first,
天晓得他要杀多少人
God knows how many people he's gonna kill.
这算什么名字啊
What kind of a name is that?
傻逼名字
Stupid name.
凯斯勒小姐
Miss Kessler.
你好大的胆子啊 跑这儿来
You got some nerve stepping back in this classroom.
我没空陪你玩
I'm not here for your games.
关掉
Turn that off!
不
No!
啊
Ah!
自我防卫 非逼我动手
Self-defense. I had to do it.
等着去校长办公室喝茶吧
I'll see you in the principal's office.
谁让你惹我的死孩子
That's what you get for fucking with me, missy.
女士
Ma'am.
滚蛋吧 猪猡
Fuck off, piggies.
他是不是在这里 -是的
- Is this where he is? - Yeah.
他就要从木工教室出来了
He'll be getting out of woodshop.
哇哦 我穿的什么啊
Whoa. What am I wearing?
给我站住
Stop right there.
救命啊 救命啊 我的天啊 布利斯菲尔德屠夫在这里
Help! Help! Oh, my God! It's the Blissfield Butcher!
-救命救命 -不许动
- Help me! Help! - Freeze!
-快跑 -救命啊 是他
- Run! - Please help! It's him!
-快快快快快 -车在哪里
- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go! - Where's the car?
跑啊 -快点快点
- Run! - Hurry! Hurry!
-快快快快 -上车
- Go, go, go, go, go! - Get in the car!
怎么回事
What's wrong with it?
烂车一辆 你要我怎么办嘛
It's a piece of shit! What do you want from me?
呃 大伙们
Uh, guys...
-嘿 哇哇哇哇 -快点
- Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa! - Hurry!
-开 开 快开 -开
- Go. Go. Go now. - Go, go!
开 开 开 开 小心
Go, go, go, go, go, go! Watch out!
嫌疑犯在一辆破车里
Suspect-suspect spotted in a shit heap!
从学校出发朝西驶去
Headed west from the high school!
为什么我就不能过个正常的生活
Why can't I just have a normal life?
-冷静点 -别跟我说冷静奈拉
- Calm down. - Don't tell me to calm down, Nyla.
我才刚满十八岁就要坐牢了
I just turned 18. I could go to prison.
奈拉你座位能移前面一点吗
Nyla, can you scooch your seat up just a little bit?
好了我们需要一个计划
Okay, we need a plan.
他们看到我们和她在一起 所以他们现在肯定在找我们
They saw us with her, so they're gonna be looking for us now.
-﻿奈拉 你能再往前移一点吗 -我们得给你乔装打扮一下米莉
- Ny, can you move up a little more? - We need to get you a disguise, Mill.
你不能穿着这身衣服 带着这张脸在外面走来走去
You can't be walking around in those clothes with that face.
所有人都认识你 -好计划
- Everyone knows who you are. - Good plan.
奈拉你能不能 再往前稍微移一丢丢
Nyla, could you just do just a little, teeny, teeny,
就一丢丢好吗
teeny, teeny, just a little bit more?
你还好吗米莉 -嗯好多了
- You good, Mill? - Yeah. Much better.
嫌疑犯与两名青少年在一起
Suspect spotted with two youths.
青少年 一个黑人女性 一个白人
Teenagers. One Black, female, one white, uh, excited.
朝镇上的西北方向驶去
Heading towards the northwest corner of town.
嘿 搞什么飞机 你在逗我玩吗
Hey, what the fuck? Are you kidding me?
我操
Shit.
什么 -警察
- What? - It's the police.
天啊 是夏琳 -呃
- Oh, my God. It's Char. - Um...
噢 朝前开左转
Ooh! Up ahead, turn left.
我们可以混进停车场里 -不不不不 那是我妈的
- We can mix into the parking lot. - No, that's my mom's...
这是我们最好的机会了 冲 -转弯
- It's our best chance! Go! - Turn!
我靠
Holy shit!
快点
Come on!
伯南扎折扣店欢迎
Discount Bonanza just wanted to welcome
所有顾客购买我们的最新
all shoppers to our new...
天啊我们死定了
Oh, my God. We're dead.
赶紧的我们得继续跑
Come on. We got to keep moving.
噢
Oh.
妈的 -赶紧走
- Shit. - Let's go.
走 走  走 走 走
Go. Go, go, go, go, go.
米莉 躲那里面去 快
Millie, hide in here. Quick.
我们不来 你就别出来
Do not come out until we get you.
走 走 走
Look, come on. Come on, come on.
女装部 请到四号柜台
Ladieswear to register four.
-噢  -噢 噢
- Oh! - Oh! Oh!
-噢 不好意思 -我很抱歉
- Oh, I'm so sorry. I... - Sorry. So sorry.
我不知道里面有人
I didn't know anybody was in there.
真抱歉 -没关系 没事
- So sorry. - No problem. Okay.
您在里边还好吗
You all good in there?
嗯 好极了
Yeah, uh, uh, great, actually.
谢谢谢谢 -没事
- Thank you. Thank you. - Sure, sure.
在试穿马球衫呢
Just, uh, trying on, uh, polos.
哇哦
Wow.
我刚好很擅长帮男士挑选马球衫噢
I happen to be a professional at helping men pick out polos.
-需要我帮忙吗 -不用了
- What do you say? - Nope.
不用 我能行 -别客气啊
- No, actually, I'm all good. - Don't be silly.
每个人都需要不同的意见还合身吗
Everybody needs a second opinion. How is the fit?
我们这有很多尺码
Because we have lots of sizes here.
噢 你知道吗 好玩的是
Oh, you know what? It's so funny.
有一年圣诞节 我给我老公买了件粉色的马球衫
I bought my husband a pink polo one year for Christmas ,
他差点晕死粉色 他那么阳刚的一个人
and he about died. "Pink?" He's so macho.
但是你猜怎么着 他穿上后看起来可帅了
But guess what. It looked great on him.
特别衬他的眼睛
Brought out his eyes.
他有一双蓝色的眼睛
He had these... these blue eyes.
他一定喜欢极了
I bet he loved it.
一定是他最喜欢的一件衣服
I bet it was his favorite shirt.
他一年前去世了
He passed away a year ago.
噢 天啊 真不好意思
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
听听我说的话黛比·唐纳我真抱歉
Listen to me. Debbie Downer. I'm sorry.
我不是有意要跟你分享这些事的
I didn't mean to share all that with you.
我只是 你只是想买件马球衫
I just... You're just... You're trying to buy a polo,
天啊 -不不不不不
- for God's sake. I... - No, no, no, no. No.
没关系的 没关系的
No, it's okay. It's okay.
我 呃 我也失去了亲人
I, um... I lost somebody, too.
真的吗 -嗯
- Really? - Yeah.
我失去了父亲 -真抱歉
- I lost my dad. - I'm so sorry.
你一定很想念他
You must miss him so much.
是的
Yeah, I do.
真的很无助对吧
Nothing prepares you for this stuff, right?
我们都被丢在那里
I mean, we're all just left here...
拼凑破碎的内心
...to pick up the pieces and...
我的大女儿 她自闭了 借工作逃避现实
My oldest, she shut down. She retreated into work.
我另一个女儿米莉 她现在特别沉默
And my other daughter, Millie, she's so quiet now.
我搞不懂她脑子里的想法
I can't figure out what's going on inside her head.
也许她只是需要一些空间吧
Maybe she just needs some... some space.
要一些时间去搞清楚她自己是谁
Just some time to figure out who she is.
是啊
Yeah.
我想我确实让她感觉压抑吧
I guess I do smother her.
我不是有意的 但是我很害怕
I don't mean to. But I am scared.
她就要高中毕业
She'll be graduating high school
去上大学了 到时候就会丢下我
and running off to college, and then I'll be left here.
一个人在这里
All by myself.
不会那样的
But that-that's never gonna happen.
她是你女儿
She's your daughter, and...
她是爱你的
...she loves you.
谢谢你这么说
Thank you for that.
你是个很好的倾诉对象 -你也很棒
- You're so easy to talk to. - Yeah, you're great. You're just...
你的声音太令人宽慰了
Your voice, it's so... comforting
也非常有男人味
and... very manly.
我知道这有点唐突 但是
I know this is awkward, uh, but...
跟你聊天真的很开心
I've had such a good time talking to you.
是啊 -我们几乎不认识彼此
- Yeah, it's been... - We hardly know each other.
-我知道我知道 -是啊
- I know, I know. - Yeah.
我甚至都还没见过你
And I, I haven't even seen you yet
但是我觉得我们之间有共鸣
but I think we have a connection, and...
我想知道你愿不愿意
I would like to know if maybe you would like to
跟我一块去喝杯咖啡什么的
grab a coffee with me sometime.
呕 天啊不
Ew. God, no.
不我不会 -我真不该问你
- No, I wouldn't, um... - I should never have asked you.
简直太不适合了 -我想说的是
- That was totally inappropriate. - And so what I'm saying is,
呃 噢 不
you know, um, "Oh, no."
我没意识到 因为我们之间有共鸣
Like, I've missed out because we've had a connection.
你的倾诉是那么美妙
You share so beautiful.
我想和你不止是喝咖啡
And I just would love to do more than a coffee.
而是 而是吃顿晚饭
Um, even, even, have a dinner?
噢 晚饭 -是啊 我会非常愿意
- Oh. Dinner? - Yeah, I would love that,
因为我感觉我们已经很了解彼此了
'cause I feel like we know each other so well.
你懂我的意思吗 就像是 -我也感觉到了
- You know what I mean? So it's like... - I feel that, too.
光咖啡对我们来说是不够的 但是我结婚了
A coffee wouldn't be enough for us. But I'm married.
噢 我是个已婚男人
- Oh. - So I'm a married man.
妈什么
- Mom! - What?
你今天有和米莉联系过吗
Have you talked to Millie today?
没还没有 -好吧 你手机在哪里
- No, I haven't. - Okay. Where's your phone?
-不在我包里 -去拿来
- No, it's in my purse. - Go get it.
打电话给她确保她是安全的
- Call her and make sure she's okay. - I will!
我这就去 -杀手刚现身了
The killer was just sighted again.
走快走祝祝你好运
- Go. Let's go. Come on. - Good luck to you!
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
快点 戴上 你现在是吓人的亚伦·罗杰斯
Quick, put it on. You're scary Aaron Rodgers now.
谁 -著名的四分卫
- Who? - Famous quarterback.
绿湾队连我都知道
- Green Bay Packers. - Even I know that.
你知道我讨厌体育
You know I hate sports.
这太可怕了我没法呼吸了
This is terrifying. I can't breathe.
我们只有时间给你搞来这个你姐在追我们呢
It's all we had time to grab. Your sister's on our ass.
我们走吧快点
- Let's go. - Come on.
我什么都看不见
I can't see shit.
杀手是怎么戴着面具杀人的
How do killers do this?
奈拉 开车
Nyla, drive.
我要刷下ins
I'm trolling Insta.
总有人知道屠夫在哪里
Somebody's got to know where The Butcher is.
好的
Got it.
噢 我操
Oh! Fuck!
噢 抱歉 哎哟 碰到你脸了 好吧
Oh! Sorry. Oh, that's your face. Okay.
好吧 我要摘下来 我什么都看不到了
Okay, I'm getting this off. I can't see anything.
哇 哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop, stop.
住手 你要是被认出来 我们就完了
If you get recognized, we are screwed.
-找到了 -天啊 什么
- Bingo. - Oh, my God. What?
窒息了这是谁啊米莉
- Suffocating. Who's this one? - Mill.
你们谁是谁啊 那是谁啊 -现场直播咯
- Which one's who? Who's that? - Coming at you live,
布利斯菲尔德非官方的返校节女王
Blissfield's unofficial homecoming queen.
太没劲了
This sucks.
我想参加派对 -我们应该自己举办返校节舞会
- I want to party. - We should throw our own homecoming.
去他妈的屠夫 -好了 当然
- Fuck The Butcher. - Okay, sure.
那我们要去哪里举办呢现在有宵禁呢
And where are we gonna pull that off with Larkin's curfew?
老厂房
The old mill.
没人会关注那里的
No one would look there.
可以啊太天才了不错哟
- Hell yeah. That's genius. - Not bad.
谁能想到咱的米莉·凯斯勒小妞那么能干呢
Who knew little Millie Kessler could be such a crafty beaver?
你的咸猪手让我的逼比砂纸还干燥
Your touch makes this pussy drier than sandpaper,
你个臭猴子
you fucking monkey.
e我迫不及待想杀你了
I can't wait to kill you.
她就是馋我身子
She fucking wants me.
我要去上个厕所
I'm gonna take a piss.
行当然咯
Okay. Sure.
我去看下后面
Okay, I'll go check the back.
好
Okay.
天啊
Oh, my God.
他要杀了他 -啥
- He's gonna kill him. - What?
他要杀了他我真的听不懂你说的
- He's gonna kill him! - I literally can't understand you.
拿着分开行动自求多福你走那边
Here. Divide and survive. You go that way.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 米莉
Hey, Millie.
你去哪里了
Where'd you go?
米莉
Millie?
伯克
Booker?
妈的
Fucking...
噢
Oh!
我他妈真讨厌这地方
I fucking hate this place.
嘿 米莉吗
Hey, Millie?
嘿 你在哪里
Hey, where are you?
我只是我只想跟你说说话
I just w... I just want to talk.
确保你没事
Make sure you're okay.
伯克
Booker!
天啊
Oh, my God.
别让他跑了他会去报警的
Don't let him get away! He'll call the cops!
救命救命
Help! Help! Help!
天啊
Oh, my God.
你哪里学的这玩意儿
Where the hell did you learn how to do that?
我爸以前参加过老鹰童子军
Dad was an Eagle Scout.
找着了这些东西
Found these.
啊
Ah.
啊哈好了
Uh-huh. Okay.
他昏过去的样子也这么帅
He's even gorgeous when he's unconscious.
嘿-﻿我的妈
- Hey. - Jesus Chr...
淡定 淡定 淡定
Easy, easy, easy.
没事的没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
听着 我知道我看起来像屠夫 但我是米莉
Look, I know I look like The Butcher, but it's Millie.
这听起来会很奇怪 -伯克
- This is gonna sound really strange. - Booker.
伯克 看着我 他疯了
Booker, look at me. He's crazy.
好了 伯克 你能看着我吗 拜托了
Okay. Booker, can you look at me, please?
拜托 伯克 拜托了 你能看着我吗
Please. Booker, please. Can you look at me?
就一小会儿
Just for a second?
昨天晚上 我们的意识或者我们的灵魂
Okay, so last night, our consciousness or our spirit,
不管你想称它为什么
whatever you want to call it...
好吧它们互换了位置
Okay? It traded places.
她说的是实话 -他拿多拉捅了我一刀
- She's telling the truth. - So, he stabbed me with the Dola,
就是一把远古的神秘匕首
which is, like, this ancient mystical dagger.
现在我只剩不到六小时的时间来互换了
And now I have, like, less than six hours to swap back,
否则我就会永远困在这幅躯壳里
or I'm gonna be stuck in his body forever.
你们都要坐牢了 你也是伯克
You're all going to jail for this. You, too, Booker.
除非你帮我伯克
Unless you help me. Booker.
省省吧 贱人 -伯克 救命啊 伯克
- Dry up, bitch. - Booker, help! Booker!
你能闭嘴吗伯克
- Will you shut up? - Booker.
我知道这很疯狂好吗 好几个声音在各说各话
Look, I know this is crazy, okay? And there's a lot of voices competing.
你看到我们朋友们了 你认识奈拉和乔什的
You see my friends, you know Nyla and Josh,
他们都是站在我这边的好吗 那明显不是我
and they're on my side, okay? And this is clearly not me.
你有见我穿过那种衣服吗
Have you ever seen me dressed like that?
我想说 他打扮的我还挺喜欢的
I mean, I kind of like a lot of what he's doing
但是关键是你从来没见过
with it, but it's... The point is that you've never seen me
我穿成那样对吧 你喜欢那样子吗
dressed like that, right? Do you like that?
算了 不重要 听着 我现在告诉你很多信息
It doesn't matter. Like, look, I'm giving you a lot of information,
你也才刚醒过来
and you literally just woke up.
呼你看起来真帅
Whew. You look great.
我 我要离开这里 -伯克 伯克 求你了
- I need to get out of here. - Booker. Booker, please.
拜托 求你了 伯克 -不 我现在就要走
- Please. Please, Booker. - No, I need to go right now.
你不要阻止我 我要发疯了好吗
You're not gonna stop me. I'm gonna freak out, okay?
我不属于你
"I'm not yours,
也没有迷恋
"not lost in you.
尽管我渴望沉醉
"Not lost, although I long to be.
如正午的烛火
"Lost as a candle lit at noon.
如汪洋中的雪花
"Lost as a snowflake in the sea.
你爱我 我也知晓
"You love me, and I find you
你仍是那个美丽而明亮的灵魂
"still a spirit, beautiful and bright.
而我依旧渴望
"Yet I am, who long to be
如一束光迷失于光芒万丈
"lost as light is lost in light.
将我投入爱的深渊吧
"Plunge me deep into love.
抹掉我的理智
"Put away my senses.
让我耳聋眼迷
"Leave me deaf and blind,
卷入你爱的暴风雨里
"swept by the tempest of your love...
做狂风中的
"...a taper...
一支纤烛
in the rushing wind."
怎么会
How?
我跟你说过这是个诅咒
I told you it was a curse.
呃
Um...
什么玩意儿啊
What the hell was that?
几个星期前 我在我的储物柜里发现了一首诗
A few weeks ago, I found a poem in my locker.
是匿名的
It was anonymous.
我也不知道我为什么要那样做
I don't know why I did it. I just was...
我只是
You know, it was...
只是太蠢了
It was just stupid.
你个可怜的臭娘们
You sad fucking cunt.
往他储物柜里放一首诗
A poem in his locker?
你个可悲的胆小鬼
You pathetic coward.
你说的够多了这个可以成为他新的嫌犯照
- That's quite enough of that. - This should be his new mug shot.
嗯
Mmm.
别乱搞了
Stop messing around.
那么匕首在警察局
So the Dola's here at the station.
我们得想办法把它偷出来
We're gonna have to figure out how to steal it
然后再带到这里来
and then get it back here.
来回差不多四十分钟吧
That's, like, 40 minutes round-trip.
时间还是充足的对吧
There's plenty of time, right?
呃 万一警察局里有人
Uh, that's assuming there's someone at the station.
嗯
Hmm.
一边在找我们 一边又要管今晚的派对
I mean, with them looking for us and the party tonight,
-警察们肯定都很忙 -嗯
- the cops could have their hands full. - Hmm.
派对在哪 -在一个老厂房里
- Where's the party? - It's at the old mill.
我在这个身体里醒来的时候 就在那个地方
That's where I woke up in this body.
他在引诱他们过去 这是个陷阱
He's luring them there. That's a trap.
那我们最好赶紧行动了 -那她怎么办
- Then we better get moving. - And what about her?
代词用错了 -服了 那他怎么办
- Pronouns. - Christ, what about him?
我妈出远门了 周一前都不会回来
My mom's out of town until Monday.
不行 我觉得把他一个人
Yeah. No, I don't think it's a good idea
扔在这不妥 -他说的对
- to leave him here alone. - No, he's right.
得有人留在这看着他
Someone needs to stay behind and keep an eye on him
以防万一 -嗯哼
- just in case. - Mmm-hmm.
啥 我吗 -这是你家
- What? Me? - It's your house.
这次绝对死定了
Definitely gonna die this time.
淡定点 你会没事的
Chill out. You'll be fine.
等等 伙计们
Wait. Wait, guys.
真棒
Great.
留我一人和杀人狂芭比待一起
Leave me alone with Murder Barbie.
好了 大伙们 他走了
Okay, guys. He's gone.
那是夏琳的车 -你们待在这里
- That's Char's car. - You guys stay here.
要是有风吹草动 就按两下喇叭好吗
Honk the horn twice if you see anything, okay?
你怎么打算的
What's your plan?
别操心那个了
Don't worry about it.
我能搞定
I got this. Yeah.
我这辈子从来没有同时那么紧张 又那么兴奋过
I've never been so stressed and excited at the same time in my life.
标签 紧张又兴奋
Hashtag "stress-cited."
标签 钢铁般的神经
Hashtag "nerves of steel."
标签 她在干什么
Hashtag "What's she doing?"
天啦 夏琳 救命啦
Oh, my God. Char, help me!
奈拉 怎么回事啊
Nyla. What the hell is going on?
你被看到和屠夫在一起
You were spotted with The Butcher.
他他绑架了我们 他威胁我们载他 我
He kidnapped us. He made us drive him. I...
我逃走了 但是他跟着我过来了
I escaped, but he followed me here.
等等 他到这儿来了 -就在外面警察局的后面
- Wait. He's here? - Outside, behind the station.
好 好 你待在这里行吗
Okay, okay. Just, just stay here, okay?
躲我桌子下面 -好的
- Hide under my desk. - Okay.
快去 快去
Go! Go, go, go!
那太疯狂了
That's so crazy.
但是我不得不承认 从某种非常奇葩的方面来说
But, you know, I have to admit, in a really strange way,
这种体验也不是完全糟糕的
that it hasn't been all bad.
怎么说 -我不知道
- What do you mean? - I don't know.
就是
It's just, you know,
在这个身体里 我感到自己非常强大
I felt oddly empowered being in this body.
好像自己很无敌
Like, invincible
或者很牛逼的那种
or kind of badass.
我知道
I know. It's, um...
这很可笑但是
I mean, it's ridiculous, but, uh...
我猜当你
I guess when you're, uh...
当你成为我这样的人
When you're someone like me and you,
人生中大部分时候都是被欺负
you know, you've been bullied most of your life
然后又默默忍受的那种
and, you know, sort of just put down a lot, that,
你懂的能有一次机会体会到强大的感觉
you know, it does feel kind of good to
还真的挺不错的
just feel strong for once.
力量并不来自于体型大小
Strength doesn't come from size.
不是的力量来自于这里
It doesn't. It comes from up here
还有那里
and in there.
而你比你想象中要强大的多
And you are a lot stronger than you think.
你好 -噢 哇哦
- Hello. - Oh, whoa! Oh!
噢 噢
Oh! Oh!
噢 天啦怎么啦
- Oh, my God. - What happened?
-卢安 你没事吧 -这个是活的
- Luann, are you okay? - This one's a live one.
我知道 等下 -你没事吧
- I know. Hold on. - Are you okay?
你那邪恶的小眼神吓不倒我
That nasty stare does not scare me.
它想把我挤下去
He just started trying to buck me off.
布利斯菲尔德扶轮社为您带来
The Blissfield Rotary Club presents...
-﻿哈 -魔法坏女巫在安妮丝剧院的现场直播
- Ha. - ...WICKED live at the Anis Theater.
赶紧来抢票吧
Get your tickets before they fly away.
女士们 我们都碰到过这种情况
Ladies, we've all been there.
-不要 -长了鸡眼
- Just... - Can't get those corns...
-动  -穿不进新鞋
- ...don't move. - ...into that new pair of shoes?
为您介绍鸡眼消除霜
Well, introducing Corn Erase.
将乳霜均匀涂抹于鸡眼上
You apply the cream all over the bunion,
在几分钟之内就会深入渗透到
and within minutes, the deep-penetrating...
我回来咯
Hello!
乔什
Joshy!
Josh.
嗨 妈
Hi, Mom.
你提早回家了
You're home early.
最后一班航班取消了
My last flight got canceled.
宝贝 为什么米莉被绑在我的餐椅上
Honey, why is Millie tied to my dining chair?
呃 她
Um, she...
我们在玩角色扮演
We, um,
嗯你说什么
role-play.
我们在进行角色扮演 -角色扮演
- Mmm? - I'm sorry?
是的角色扮演
- We're role-playing. - Role-playing?
是个游戏吗
Yes, role-playing.
算是吧
- Like a game? - Sort of.
她看起来好像玩得不怎么开心
She doesn't look like she's enjoying herself.
噢
- Oh.
本来就是这样
Oh, um, that, that's the point.
她本来就要表现出不安的样子
She's, she's supposed to act upset.
对吧 米莉
Right, Millie?
她演的很好永远不跳出角色
She's method. Never breaks character.
坏姑娘
Naughty girl!
他在吃我的手镯
He's eating my bracelet!
我有点疑惑了
I'm a little confused.
难道角色扮演
Isn't role-playing...
不是性游戏吗
...a sex game?
是吗 -嗯哼
- Is it? - Mmm-hmm.
是的
Yes. Yes, it is.
嗯哼 对
Mmm-hmm. Yep.
那么
So...
好吧 呃
Okay, um,
妈 我没准备好之前是不想告诉你的 但是
Mom, I didn't want to tell you until I was ready,
我是直男
but I'm straight.
乔舒亚 你怎么都不可能是直男
Joshua, you are many things, but straight isn't one of them.
现在帮我个忙 把她松开吧
Now, do me a favor and untie her.
我做不到 -乔舒亚
- I can't. - Joshua!
妈 对不起
Mom, I'm sorry.
我现在跟你解释不清 但是我不能放他走
I can't explain right now, but I cannot let him go.
他 -不是 妈
- "Him"? - No. Mom.
妈妈 妈 听我说
Mom, Mom, Mom, listen to me.
他是布利斯菲尔德屠夫
He's the Blissfield Butcher!
天啊 乔舒亚·迈克尔·德特莫
God! Joshua Michael Detmer,
我这一礼拜工作下来已经够累了
I've been slinging peanuts to assholes all week.
我没时间跟你胡闹
I don't have time for this.
不妈妈 妈妈 不要
No. Mom. Mom, Mom, Mom, don't.
你怎么会干这种事情啊
How did you even do this? Ow!
快跑
Run!
快 快 快 快 快
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
不 不  不 去窗户那
No, no, no, no, no! Go for the windows!
把窗都锁上 -好的
- Make sure they're locked! - Okay!
干嘛 -奈拉他跑了
- What? - Nyla, he's escaped!
什么
What?
这个身体真他妈没一点用
Body's fucking useless!
我找不到他 你确定他跟着你来了吗
I couldn't find him. Are you sure he followed you?
我确定 我发誓
Yes, I'm sure he did. I swear he...
他绑架了我们 然后
He took us, and, and...
奈拉
Nyla.
他妈的到底怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
不许接电话
Don't you dare answer that.
我可以解释的 -奈拉 这可不是儿戏
- I can explain. - Nyla, this is serious.
-把你的双手举起来 -拜托了 听我解释
- Put your hands up. - Please, just let me explain.
举起手来快点
Hands up! Now!
我要你慢慢把武器放下来
I want you to slowly set the weapon down.
踢到我这边来
Now kick it over to me.
嘿 你介意我坐后面来吗
Hey, do you mind if I come back there?
当然不介意 -是吗
- Sure. - Yeah?
我的天
My God.
好嘞我刚感觉太远了
Right. I felt so far away.
-嗯 -那么
- Hmm. - So,
关于那首诗 -噢 我的天啦
- about that poem... - Oh, my gosh.
求你别提那茬 那就是个彻头彻尾的失误
Please don't bring that up. That was a total mistake.
那是个失误
That was a mistake?
怎么 你无意间写了那首诗 然后
What? You accidentally wrote it
你经过我储物柜的时候 刚好就绊了一跤 它就掉进去了
and you were just going by my locker, and you tripped, and it fell in?
是的 就是这样
Yes, exactly. That's what happened.
我觉得挺美好的
Well, I thought it was beautiful.
那首诗
The poem.
大概有读了一百遍吧
Probably read it, like, a hundred times.
真的吗
Really?
是的虽然一开始发现它的时候 觉得有点诡异
Yeah. I mean, once I got over how creepy it was finding it, yeah.
抱歉 -我开玩笑啦
- Sorry. - I'm kidding.
那会儿其实我有点希望是你写给我的
I actually kind of hoped that it was your poem.
你才没有呢
No, you didn't.
米莉
Millie,
我从一开始就喜欢你了
I've liked you since day one.
你不用这么说的
You don't have to say that.
我知道 所以我才要告诉你
I know I don't. That's why I did.
我现在有点想亲你 是有多奇怪啊
How weird is it that I kind of feel like kissing you right now?
确切来说
Technically,
你亲的是一个满口黄牙的杀人狂魔
you'd be kissing a mass murderer with yellow teeth.
对我来说你依旧是米莉
You're still Millie to me.
也许 我们该等一等 等我的手
Maybe we should wait for when my hand's
-不比你的整张脸还大的时候 -是啊 对对对
- not bigger than your whole face. - Yeah. No, no, no.
没关系的 你想什么时候都可以
That's okay. That's... It's, it's whenever you want.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
我操
Fuck!
米莉 你他妈去哪儿了
Millie, where the fuck have you been?
我给你打了一整天的电话了 -什么
- I have been calling you all day. - What?
我也有打给你
I've been calling you, too.
这不是你妹 -奈拉 给我闭嘴
- That is not your sister. - Nyla, shut the fuck up.
好了
Okay.
这是怎么回事
What is going on here?
米莉你别插手
Millie, stay out of this.
我只想帮忙 -我不需要行吗
- I'm just trying to help. - I don't need your help, okay?
-我只想帮忙 -我他妈不需要你帮忙
- I'm just trying to help! - I don't need your fucking help.
给我往后退
Back the fuck up.
夏琳
Char!
快跑 米莉
Run, Millie!
举起手来 举起手来
Get your hands up. Hands up now!
拜托 奈拉他妈的接电话啊
Come on, Nyla. Pick up the fucking phone!
夏琳
Charlene.
夏琳 夏琳
Charlene! Charlene!
在这里 夏琳
Over here! Charlene!
天啊
Oh, my God!
给我朝牢房走过去
Start walking towards the cell.
快点
Come on!
你能听我说吗 -快点
- Can you listen to me? - Now!
奈拉 你别他妈给我乱动
Nyla, don't you fucking move!
进去
Get in.
拜托你能不能听我说 -进去
- Can you please listen to me? - Move!
嘿
Hey!
-不 -真对不起
- No! - I'm so sorry.
-噢 天啊 不 -夏琳 我很抱歉
- Oh, my God! No! - Char, I'm so sorry.
不
No!
你妈个逼的放我出去 -我真的以为
- You motherfucker! Get me out! - I really thought
你的仓鼠会游泳 很抱歉瑞格死了
your hamster could swim, and I'm so sorry that Regal died.
但是过一会儿 你就能想通了
But this is all gonna make sense to you later on.
我得走了 真的很抱歉 我爱你 么么哒
I got to run. I'm so sorry. I love you! Mwah!
大伙们
Guys, we gotta go!
我们得走了 不能让他跑了 -走 赶紧走
- We can't let him get away! - Let's go, let's go!
你的计划烂透了
Your plan's the fucking worst.
你没事吧 -你姐就是个马路杀手
- Are you okay? - Your sister's a shitty driver.
那不是夏琳是屠夫
That's not Char, that's the Butcher
他还带走了匕首 -什么
- and he's got the Dola. - What?
走吧大伙们
Come on, guys. Let's go!
呦吼吼 米莉小香草
Yo-ho-ho, Millie Vanilli.
咱伯克兄弟呢
Where's my boy Booker?
你们不是在一块儿么
Thought you guys were together.
好吧
Okay.
你以为你现在是抢手货吗
So, you think you're this hot shit now, huh?
我告诉你 没有哪个女人见了我不发骚的
You know, I've never made anyone's pussy dry.
瞧瞧我
I mean, look at me.
噢 现在你喜欢了
Oh, now you like it.
行 来吧
All right, come on.
等一下 等一下
Wait, wait.
好像没人
Looks clear.
走吧
Let's go.
你们留在这里
You guys stay here.
太危险了
This is way too dangerous.
我们不可能坐视不理 米莉
There is no way we're not helping you, Mill.
我们要一起面对
We're in this together.
还剩十三分钟了
Thirteen minutes left.
否则你就永远是屠夫了
Or you're the Butcher forever.
嘿 把你手腕给我
Hey, come here, give me your wrist.
我来设置个计时器
Let me set a timer.
噢 好的
Oh, okay.
是时候去捅这个混蛋了
Time to stab this asshole.
哟呵 没料到吧 看来我们
Well, what do you know? Looks like we got
要搞一个小小的私密派对了 不是么
a little private party going here, huh?
你数学怎么样 米莉
Uh, are you good at math, Millie?
因为在我看来
'Cause the way I see it,
你有三个洞刚刚好
you have three holes, and it all adds up.
喝点更好办事
Will make it easier.
来吧
There we go.
搞什么
What the fuck?
你他妈对我朋友做了什么 你个贱婊子
What the fuck did you do to my friends, you fucking bitch?
你要干什么
What are you doing?
哇哦嘿 哇哦
Whoa, whoa, look. Hey, whoa, whoa.
你要干什么 住手 不不不
What are you doing? Stop. No, no, no.
不要
Don't.
求你了 对不起 求你了 求你了 求你了 不
Please. I'm sorry. Please, please, please, please, no.
对不起
I'm sorry!
Look, I'm sorry!
对不起 求你了
I'm sorry! Please!
靠人也太多了
Shit, it's packed.
我们分成两队搜索 看到他就发信息
We'll search in pairs. Text if you see him.
不要莽撞行事
Do not try and be a hero.
-注意安全米莉 -你们也是
- Be careful, Mill. - You, too.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey. What's up?
你见过米莉吗
Have you seen Millie?
呃 米莉 米莉
Uh, Millie, Millie.
米莉
Millie.
噢 是的 我见过她
Oh, yeah. I, uh... I saw her.
真的吗 在哪 -呃 这边
- Really? Where? - Uh, this way.
走吧 走吧
Come on. Come on.
来吧
Come on.
我要来不及了
I'm not gonna make it.
嘿 别这么说 还有时间呢
Hey, don't say that. There's still time.
操
Sh...
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
嘿 嘿  他在这里 他杀了布雷特 还有其他几个人
Hey, hey! He's here! He killed Brett and the others.
什么 米莉在哪 -她去找乔舒亚了
- What? Where's Millie? - Uh, she went to find Joshua.
噢 糟糕
Oh, shit.
她在哪
Where is she?
你说你知道她在哪
You said you knew where she was.
她在某个地方
She's somewhere.
米莉 米莉
Millie, Millie.
米莉 米莉 米莉 米莉
Millie, Millie, Millie. Millie, Millie.
菲尔 我没时间搞这个 她在哪
Phil, I don't have time for this. Where...
傻逼基佬
Loser faggot.
哇哦
Wow!
你还真有自知之明呢 好勇敢噢
So self-aware. Bravo.
你要是告诉别人 我他妈就杀了你
You tell anybody, I'll fucking kill you.
乔什
Josh!
快走 -不
- Get out of here. - No!
你在干什么 -走
- What are you doing? - Go!
我要拿回我的身体
I want my body back.
那你过来拿啊
Come and get it.
嘿 嘿 我们找到他了
Hey. Hey. We found him.
他要杀了米莉 -走 去帮她
- He's gonna kill Millie. - Right, go help her.
我来拖延他们 -站住 别动
- I'll slow them down. - Stop right there!
快走
Come on.
住手我要捅自己啦
Stop! I'm trying to stab myself!
放下武器 -开枪
- Drop the knife! - Shoot him!
他妈的把我的身体还给我
Come back with my fucking body!
接着
Catch!
按住他
Hold him down.
不
No.
你们太迟了
You're too late.
等等
Wait.
钟声呢 -什么
- Where's the bell? - What?
钟声没敲响
The bell, uh, it didn't toll.
专业人士建议
Pro tip.
永远设置提前五分钟
Always set your watch five minutes ahead.
对我来说 很管用 几乎每一次都是
Saves my ass, like, every time.
把他按住
Hold him down.
不 不 不
No! No! No! No!
米莉
Millie?
谁是你最喜欢的运动员
Who's your favorite athlete?
他们在这里 -嘿
- They're over there! - Hey!
没有我不喜欢运动
No one. I hate sports.
不许动
Freeze!
打死这个狗东西
Shoot that motherfucker!
呃 我们这是经历了啥
Um, what the fuck just happened?
反正不是做梦
That's real.
嘿 抱歉打扰啦
Hey. Sorry to interrupt.
是时候搞定他了
Time to land that plane, girl.
嗨
Hi.
肩膀怎么样了
How's the shoulder?
实话说 痛得好
Honestly, the best pain I've ever felt.
那你跟警察怎么说呢
So, what are you gonna tell the cops?
实话实说吧
A version of the truth, I guess.
希望不会再有人拿到那玩意儿了
Let's just hope nobody ever gets their hands on that thing again.
什么
What?
那么
So,
我们之前试着要做的
that thing
那事儿
we were trying to do earlier.
噢
Oh.
Oh!
我们准备好 再来一次了吗
Oh, are we, are we ready to try that again?
我不知道 我看看
I don't know. Let's see. Let's...
好多了 -嗯
- That's much better. - Mmm.
好样的 米莉
Yeah, Mill!
米莉
Millie!
妈妈 -噢
- Mom? - Oh.
噢 米莉 你没事 我可担心坏了
Oh, Millie, you're okay. I was so worried.
他的脉搏和心率都很虚弱
His pulse and heart rate are weak.
我觉得他挺不过去了
I don't think he's gonna make it.
很好
Good.
太冷血了吧
How empathetic.
你要是见过他的罪行 你也会高兴的
If you'd seen the carnage, you'd be glad, too.
看来你如愿以偿了
Looks like you got your wish.
我累了 我要去睡觉了
I'm tired. I'm gonna hit the sack.
晚安 夏琳
Good night, Char.
嘿
Hey.
我爱你 姐姐
I love you, sis.
我也爱你 小鬼
I love you, too, stinker.
-﻿晚安 妈妈 -﻿晚安 夏琳
- Good night, Mom. - Good night, Charlene.
关于波士顿大学的申请
that application to Boston,
我是希望你去的
I want you to go.
没事的 我不是一定要去
It's okay. I don't need to go.
你是我女儿
You're my daughter.
这点是改变不了的
Nothing will ever change that.
去过你的人生吧 米莉
Live your life, Millie.
谢谢 妈
Thanks, Mom.
夏琳
Char!
你门又没关
You left the door open again.
夏琳
Char?
有人吗
Hello?
怎么了 米莉
What's the matter, Millie?
你如愿以偿了不是吗
You got what you wanted, right?
你拿回你的身体了
You got your body back.
为什么还不开心呢
Why aren't you happy?
不许动
Freeze!
小姑娘家的 不该玩枪
Little girls shouldn't play with guns.
跑 米莉 跑
Run, Millie! Run!
别停啊
Well, don't stop.
接着来啊
Keep coming.
我在你身体里待过
I've been in your body.
我明白为什么你感觉那么脆弱
I understand why you feel so weak.
那么无力
Why you feel so meager.
还有你因你爹的去世
And all that anxiety that you got.
引发的那些焦虑
Clinging to your dead dad.
你只是另一个更弱的她而已
You're really just a lesser version of her.
还要对一个醉鬼老妈言听计从
And having to take all those orders from some drunk mom.
啊 天啊 啊
Ah! God! Ah!
那样的生活根本没有意义
That's not a life.
但是没关系
But it's all right.
没事
It's okay.
我们可以解决的
We'll fix it.
你知道么
You know...
在你身体里的时候 我也学到了些东西
I learned something when I was in your body, too.
什么
What's that?
有蛋不是件好事
Having balls sucks.
抓住我的手
Take my hand!
米莉
Millie!
妈呀 米莉
Damn, Mill.
我他妈的屌爆了
I am a fucking piece.